Finding aid to the Rosemary Keefe papers SSC.MS.00680
Sophia Smith Collection
Rosemary Keefe papers
1960-2011
Sophia Smith Collection
Keefe Curb, Rosemary, 1940-2012
SSC.MS.00680
8.042 linear feet (10 containers)
Rosemary Keefe (1940-2012) was a feminist scholar and pioneer in the field of women's studies as well as a social justice activist. She was a former Catholic nun who left her order, married, had a daughter, divorced and ultimately came out as a lesbian. Keefe became nationally known with the 1985 publication of the controversial book Lesbian Nuns: Breaking the Silence, which she wrote with Nancy Manahan. The Rosemary Keefe papers include personal and professional correspondence, publications, biographical materials, play reviews, clippings, flyers and posters, calendars, women's studies materials, photos, and audio recordings, including her extensive feminist theater research archives.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use without restriction beyond the standard terms and conditions of Smith College Special Collections. Parts of the collection are stored offsite; researchers must give 48 hours advance notice.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Smith College received these papers from Rosemary Keefe in 2011, and from her long-time partner Doris Burkemper in 2015.
Biographical Note
Rosemary Keefe (1940-2012) was a feminist scholar and pioneer in the field of women's studies. She was a former Catholic nun who left her order, married, had a daughter, divorced and ultimately came out as a lesbian. The last twenty years of her life she used her family name, Keefe, rather than Rosemary Curb, her married name. Keefe became nationally known after the 1985 publication of Lesbian Nuns: Breaking Silence, an anthology of the experiences of about 50 nuns and former nuns, which she wrote with Nancy Manahan. After appearances on national television, including The Phil Donahue Show, the book gained the cache of being "banned in Boston" due to pressure by the Catholic Church there, a distinction that caused book sales to soar.
Keefe received her BA in biology from Rosary College, part of Dominican University in Illinois, in 1962. As Sister Mary Geralda, O.P., she taught high school biology, religion, and English courses until 1965 when she left the order and returned to school. She went on to earn a Master's degree and her PhD in English from the University of Arkansas. For the next thirty years, taught English and women's studies, including at Rollins College, where she also served as director of Women's Studies from 1979 to 1992 and at the University of Wisconsin-Superior from 2000 to 2007. A staunch advocate for civil rights, her dissertation was entitled "The American Dream in Afro-American Drama: 1960-1970." Keefe entered the field of women's studies just as it was developing and was a prolific scholar whose research focused primarily on feminist and lesbian theater. In addition to Lesbian Nuns: Breaking Silence(1985) and Amazon All Stars: Thirteen Lesbian Plays(1996), which she edited, Keefe published hundreds of articles on feminist theater and women playwrights. An activist as well as an author, she served as president of the Orlando, Florida, chapter of the National Organization for Women and the Southeast Women's Studies Association and was active in the anti-nuclear peace movement.
Scope and Contents
These papers include personal and professional correspondence, which give a unique lens into the personal challenges, strategies and analysis of feminist and lesbian scholars and activists, especially writers and other women working in feminist theater. The collection includes some biographical materials such as CV's, awards, letters of recommendation, and job appointment letters as well as Keefe's play reviews, clippings, calendars, women's studies and other teaching materials, photographs, and audio recordings of interviews for books, including Lesbian Nuns: Breaking the Silence, the controversial 1985 book she wrote with Nancy Manahan, as well as other projects. Keefe wrote extensively on women playwrights and feminist theater companies and productions and the feminist theater archives which she assembled as research for that work is included in the collection.
Arrangement
Materials in this collection were arranged into four series, Personal, Professional, Writings and Research: Feminist Theater.
Feminist theater -- United States -- History -- Sources; Lesbians'writings, American; Women dramatists, American -- 20th century; Women in the theater -- United States -- History -- Sources; Ephemera; Newspapers; Periodicals; Playbills; Plays; Publications; Research; Feminism--History-20th century-Sources; Brochures; articles; Theater--United States--History--20th century--Sources; Feminism and theater--United States--History--Sources; Notes; Pamphlets; Lesbian feminism--United States--History--Sources; correspondence; Keefe Curb, Rosemary, 1940-2012; Burkemper, Doris; Keefe Curb, Rosemary, 1940-2012; Burkemper, Doris
- Series I. Personal, 1968-2001
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes materials from Keefe's schooling, CVs, correspondence and other materials concerning job searches, personal correspondence as well as literature regarding anti-nuclear and peace movement activities and consciousness raising workshop materials, including a personal statement.
  - Copies of BA and MA degrees, 1969; 1972 (Box 1)
  - CVs, undated (Box 1)
  - Rosemary Keefe Myers-Briggs completed test with related materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Letter confirming Keefe Curb's award of Human rights Watch award, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Los Angeles NOW Consciousness Raising Handbook, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Consciousness raising materials including articles, workshop materials and personal statement by Keefe Curb, 1982-1991 (Box 1)
  - Consciousness raising materials related to violence against women, 1983-1989 (Box 1)
  - Materials related to the Pagoda women's community in St. Augustine, Florida including personal correspondence, newsletters, financial reports, 1985-1988 (Box 1)
  - Materials related to peace activism including event flyers, Women's Encampment and other newsletters, poster and articles, 1981-1984 (Box 1)
  - United States Institute of Peace publication, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
  - Keefe Curb's completed Higher Education Resource Services (HERS) alumnae survey with drafts of essay question responses, 1996 (Box 1)
  - Personal correspondence, 1993-1998 (Box 1)
  - Central Florida Nuclear Freeze Campaign newsletter, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Full color poster "To Stop the Cruise and Pershing Missile Deployment in Europe," Seneca Women's Encampment, 1983 (Box 10)
- Series II. Professional, 1970-2009
  This series includes materials from Keefe's years as a womens studies professor, professional correspondence, awards, and articles about Keefe.
  - Short story and related letters by Keefe Curb at center of dispute at Missouri Southern College, 1976-1979 (Box 1)
  - Rollins College professor evaluation, CV and personal statement, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Program listing Keefe Curb talk on James Baldwin for "A Black Theater Conference" at the University of Massachusetts, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, applications, and letters of recommendation related to job searches, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - Letters of recommendation and other materials related to job searches, 1997-1999 (Box 1)
  - Campus interview schedules and related materials, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Materials related to Spelman and Emory Colleges job applications, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Offer from Merrimack College of Dean of Faculty of Liberal Arts position and related materials, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, research and other materials related to job searches, 2000-2004 (Box 1)
  - Personal correspondence, women's studies and other class materials and letter of resignation, Rollins College, Rutgers University, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - Reading list and other materials for "Mothers and Daughters in Literature and Film" class, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Letter offering Keefe appointment as Dean of Faculty at University of Wisconsin Superior and correspondence and notes related to a mediation process, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
  - Clippings, flyers, calendars and other materials related to Dean of Faculty position at University of Wisconsin, 2000-2002 (Box 1)
  - Calendar and material related to conference travel, 2000-2001 (Box 1)
  - Keefe essay, "What is the Value of Studying the Liberal Arts?", 2001 (Box 1)
  - Article, "Deliberate Dialogue to Expand Civic Dialogue," by Martha McCoy and Patrick L Scully, with related material, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Syllabus, Phyllis Tuchman article on Frida Kahlo, and other materials for women's studies seminar, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Faculty development seminar material, 2004 (Box 1)
  - North Central Association of Colleges and Schools report on University of Wisconsin-Superior, 2004 (Box 1)
  - University of Wisconsin faculty mentoring publication and related materials, 1996 (Box 1)
  - Keefe memorandum University of Wisconsin requesting clarification of responsibilities as Dean of Faculty Development, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Letter appointing Keefe Wisconsin Teaching Scholar, 2005 (Box 1)
  - Flyer for "Ageism as Discrimination: A Feminist Critique" program with related materials, 2009 (Box 1)
  - University of Canterbury women's studies proposal with related materials and correspondence regarding Fulbright Scholarship, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Women's studies material from Ireland including flyers, book covers and articles, 1990 (Box 1)
  - National Women's Studies Association mailing labels and related material, 1988; 1990 (Box 1)
  - Martha Boesing correspondence, clippings and other material, 1996; 2004 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Audre Lorde with article and poems, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Keefe's 'Letters to Save' file, 1977-1979 (Box 1)
  - Professional correspondence, 1981-1986 (Box 1)
  - "Letters to Save" file, 1970-1979 (Box 1)
  - Professional correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 1)
  - Professional correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 1)
  - Professional and personal correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Box 2)
  - National Women's Studies Association (NWSA) conferences material including correspondence, flyers, publications, and presentation notes, 2000-2009 (Box 2)
  - Photos of lesbian artists, 1980's (Box 2)
  - Graphics and cartoons, undated (Box 2)
  - International Women's Playwrights Conference materials including poster, correspondence and contact list, 1993-2003 (Box 2)
  - Audio recording of Cathie Dunsford / Miriam Saphira Interviews in Auckland, NZ with Curb, 1988 August 29-30; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Renee - Radio N1 interview audio recording, 1989; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Women of Power, Split Britcher Company audio recording, 1989 August 11; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Race and Class - Buffalo, NY, audio recording, 1988 October 21; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Rosemary Curb interviews Alison and Linda, part 1, audio recording, 1990; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Robert Ray "Postmodernism and Intellectual History" audio recording, 1991 February 22; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Postmodernism in the Theatre: Pt. II audio recording, 1990; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Audio recording of WKKO Boston radio interview with Rosemary, 1985 April 4; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Audio recording of Sue and Romy interview, 1985; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Lesbian Theory NWSA, audio recording, 1988; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Audio recording of Lesbian Poetry Session - Melanie Kaye, Sanoy Boucher, 1980; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Opening Plenary: Life Itself audio recording, 1985; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Translation of interview in DIVA: Rosemary and Nancy audio recording, 1986 March; 2 items (2 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Audio recording of Lesbian Theatre: Black Feminist Criticism, 1989 August; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - R. Curb interviews Alison and Linda on Lesbian History and Culture in AOTEAROA, audio recording, 1990; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Audio recording of Rosemary and Mary Huny Hollow, 1987 December 17; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Susan Griffin interview with P. Mael and R. Curb, audio recording, 1980; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Audio recording of Black American Lit. Adrienne Kennedy, 1985; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Audio recording of Lesbianism and Religious life: Three Personal Statements - Wallen, Butler, Curb, 1982 April 22; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Henderson Celebration, audio recording, 1987; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Rosemary Curb / Sound interview audio recording, 1990; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 7)
  - Audio recording of Radio Station KRCL 91FM interview with Rosemary Curb, 2 Parts, 1988 November 30; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - Audio recording of Women and Power Conference: Jessie and Fran talk with Rosemary, 1986 June 6; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - Interview with Rosemary Keefe Curb - KUMO audio recording, 1985; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - Audio recording of The Singing Nun, 1980; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - Audio recording of Rosemary - Interview / Earlier, 1990; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - R. Curb journal - Okarito Trip audio recording, 1990 October 19; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - Rosemary Curb - Intended Lecture, audio recording, 1990 August 7; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - NWSA "Danger, Power and Vision" audio recording, 1989 June 16; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - Invocation to Free Women - Felicity Artemis Flowers and Ruth Barrett audio recording, 1985; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - Audio recording of 11th Annual NWSA Convention, 1985; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - Audio recording of West Coast LN Gathering, 1986 June 4; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - R. Curb "Silence / Absence" in the Politics of Gender audio recording, 1988 February 16; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - Alice Childress, audio recording, 1990; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - The Women's Movement: Forum on the Future audio recording, 1985; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - Audio recording of Dr. Rosemary Curb on Mark Scott, 1985 October 4; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - NZ Women's Theatre, audio recording, 1990; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - Audio recording of Spare Tyre - Eat it if you want to!, 1974; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - Audio recording of WMNF Women's Show, Tampa, FL. - Rosemary Curb, 1980; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 8)
  - Class: Feminist Poets audio recording, 1981 January 27; 2 items (2 Audiocassettes) (Box 9)
  - Matriarchy at MSSC audio recording, 1985; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 9)
  - Audio recording of Adrienne Rich - Planetarium: A Retrospective (1950-1980), 1986; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 9)
  - Audio recording of Adrienne Rich - Tracking the Contradictions: Poems (1981-1985), 1986; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 9)
  - Audio recording of Fire in the Future: A musical re/vision of Joan of Arc, 1988 February 26; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 9)
  - Hurrah for Woman Suffrage! 1848-1920, audio recording, 1995; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 9)
  - Audio recording of interview at KB00 Portland, 1985 June 14; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 9)
  - Audio recording of Are We Really Out of the Closet?, 1985; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 9)
  - Clare Coss interview audio recording, 1989; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 9)
  - Audio recording of 10th Annual NWSA Convention, 1990; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 9)
  - Audio recording of 9th Annual NWSA Convention, 1985; 2 items (2 Audiocassettes) (Box 9)
  - Martha Boesing in feminist theatre, audio recording, 1980; 1 items (1 Audiocassette) (Box 9)
  - Deena Metzger, "Finding and Telling the Story" audio recording, 1983 May 20; 1 items (1 Microcassette) (Box 9)
  - Audio recording of Sue-Ellen Case on Women in Drag, 1983 May 19; 1 items (1 Microcassette) (Box 9)
  - At the Foot of the Mt. process panel, audio recording, 1983 May 18; 1 items (1 Microcassette) (Box 9)
  - Susan Weed Meditation, audio recording, 1980; 2 items (2 Microcassettes) (Box 9)
  - Fish Riding Bikes, audio recording, 1983; 1 items (1 Microcassette) (Box 9)
  - Audio recording of Stanford Women Dramatics - Chenoy, Jenkins, Cole, 1985; 1 items (1 Microcassette) (Box 9)
  - Herbert Blau, audio recording, 1990; 1 items (1 Microcassette) (Box 9)
  - "Leftovers" audio recording, 1985; 1 items (1 Microcassette) (Box 9)
  - Audio recording of Judith Katz playwriting workshop, 1983 May 17-18; 1 items (1 Microcassette) (Box 9)
  - Audio recording of Karen Malpede Lecture / Kate Hasten performance, 1980; 2 items (2 Microcassettes) (Box 9)
  - Audio recording of Jan Raymond and Pay Hynes interview, 1983 October; 1 items (1 Microcassette) (Box 9)
  - Audio recording of Martin Essline / Margaret Wilkenson, 1985; 1 items (1 Microcassette) (Box 9)
  - Audio recording of Terry Baum "Death's Angel" / Cheryl Clarke "Narratives", 1980; 1 items (1 Microcassette) (Box 9)
  - Ginny Apuzzo, audio recording, 1983 June; 1 items (1 Microcassette) (Box 9)
  - Alison Lyssa, audio recording, 1980; 1 items (1 Microcassette) (Box 9)
  - Discussion of "Sisters" by Patricia Montley, audio recording, 1983; 2 items (2 Microcassettes) (Box 9)
  - National Festival of Feminist Theatre, audio recording, 1983 May 17; 1 items (1 Microcassette) (Box 9)
  - Copy of interview with Rosemary Curb, Gay Community News, April 30, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Flyers for 1980 Womyn's Festival Theater and "Immaculate Deception," abortion-themed play, 1980-1986 (Box 6)
  - Feminist theater in America chronology and related, completed questionnaires, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
  - The Open Mind theater poster for production of Karen Malpede's A Lament for Three Women, undated (Box 10)
  - Today's Woman article "Doers and Achievers," including Keefe Curb, November, 1996 (Box 10)
  - Today's Woman article on Keefe Curb, "Woman of the Month", August, 1998 (Box 10)
- Series III. Writings, 1973-2011
  This series contains notes, correspondence, clippings of articles and play reviews by Keefe, as well as copies of her books.
  - "Where Were You the Day They Shot the President," article, Rolling Stone magazine, 1973 (Box 2)
  - Keefe Curb doctoral dissertation, The Idea of the American Dream in Afro-American Plays of the Nineteen Sixties, 1977 (Box 2)
  - Articles, reviews, papers and other writings by Keefe Curb, 1976-1993 (Box 2)
  - Book, Lesbian Nuns: Breaking the Silence, 1985 (Box 2)
  - Keefe Curb's research file on Jeannine Deckers, "The Singing Nun", 1985 (Box 2)
  - Articles by Keefe Curb, 1985-2005 (Box 2)
  - Presentation on James Baldwin, 1987 (Box 2)
  - Feminist theater entry in Feminist Companion to Literature, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Articles and reviews by Keefe Curb, 1990-1997 (Box 2)
  - Article, "No Poaching Eggs" and related material, 1992-1995 (Box 2)
  - Draft of Emory University remarks, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Book, Amazon All Stars: Thirteen Lesbian Plays, edited by Keefe Curb, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Reviews, articles and related correspondence, 1997 (Box 2)
  - "Feminists Face the Future in Retirement," by Keefe Curb with related materials, 2004 (Box 2)
  - "Talkin' Broadway" reviews, articles, playbills and related material, 2010-2011 (Box 2)
  - Memoir pieces written for Santa Fe Writing Institute class, 2011 (Box 2)
  - "The House Guest," by Keefe Curb with related materials, undated (Box 2)
  - Chapters three through eight of untitled writing project, undated (Box 2)
  - Feminist theater article, undated (Box 2)
  - The Traveler article on mime as a universal language by Curb, 1974-09-09 (Box 10)
  - Review of production of The Contrast by Curb, 1974-09-30 (Box 10)
  - The Women's Review of Books article by Curb on women's theater, 1986-06 (Box 10)
  - Belle Lettres article on Australian playwright Allison Lyssa, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Book review by Curb of A Faith of One's Own: Explorations by Catholic Lesbians, edited by Barbara Zanotti, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Book review of Going Out of Our Minds: The Metaphysics of Liberation by Sonia Johnson, 1987-10 (Box 10)
- Series IV. Research: Feminist Theatre, 1960-2010
  This series is made up of Keefe's Feminist Theater Archives as well as related materials from other batches of her orginal files, including articles and reviews, flyers, posters, photographs concerning women playwrights and feminist theater.
  - "Dora Dufran's Wild West Extravaganza" by Martha Boesing, July, 1979 (Box 2)
  - "Pimp" by Martha Boesing, undated (Box 2)
  - "The Story of a Mother" by Martha Boesing, undated (Box 2)
  - "Hunting Down the Sexes" by Joan Schenkar, undated (Box 2)
  - "Hannah Free" by Claudia Allen, 1993 (Box 2)
  - "Standing in the Shadows" by Rosemary McLaughlin, 1992 (Box 2)
  - "Angels of Power" by Sandra Shotlander, 1991 (Box 2)
  - "A Piece of Soul" by Kim Roff, 1999 (Box 2)
  - "Time Pieces" - Women's Theatre Group, undated (Box 2)
  - "American Women Playwrights: From Mercy to Megan, from Angelina to Alice" by Doris Abramson, undated (Box 2)
  - Plawright Shirlene Holmes, 2000 (Box 3)
  - "Sisters" by Susan Lersch, 1982 (Box 3)
  - "Fire in the Future" by Joan Schenkar, 1988 (Box 3)
  - "Well" by Lisa Kron - New York Times review, 2004 (Box 3)
  - "Flyin' West" by Pearl Cleage, undated (Box 3)
  - "The Second Coming of Joan of Arc" by Carolyn Gage, 1987 (Box 3)
  - "American Kings English for Queens" by Megan Terry, 1978 (Box 3)
  - "Voices" by Susan Griffin, 1975 (Box 3)
  - "The Candle Lit" by Frances Madeson, 1995 (Box 3)
  - "Film Festival" by Adrienne Kennedy, 1984 (Box 3)
  - "Tribes: A Play of Dreams" by Judith Katz, 1980 (Box 3)
  - "Split Britches" by Peggy Shaw, Deborah Margolin, Lois Weaver, 1982 (Box 3)
  - "The Rex Family: Jocasta and Oedipus" by de Helen and Kasten, 1978 (Box 3)
  - "Closer to Utopia" by Marty Kingsbury, 1982 (Box 3)
  - "Princess Cinderella" by Anna Rallo, 1980 (Box 3)
  - Snapdragon Ozark Feminist Theatre, Fayetteville, Arkansas, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Bibliography - Plays by Women, 1960-1978 (Box 3)
  - Omaha Magic Theatre, 1990 (Box 3)
  - At the Foot of the Mountain, 1986-1989 (Box 3)
  - Clare Coss, 1985-2000 (Box 3)
  - "Harriet Tubman Visits a Therapist" by Carolyn Gage, 2001 (Box 3)
  - "Stigmata" by Carolyn Gage, 2004 (Box 3)
  - "Angels of Power" by Sandra Shotlander, 1991 (Box 3)
  - "River Journal" by Martha Boesing, 1979 (Box 3)
  - "Joan" by Dorothy Hewett, undated (Box 3)
  - "Fefu and Her Friends" by Maria Irene Fornes, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Adrienne Kennedy - "A Lesson in a Dead Language", "A Rat's Mass", undated (Box 3)
  - Adrienne Kennedy - "Funnyhouse of a Negro", "The Owl Answers", undated (Box 3)
  - Adrienne Kennedy - "Cities in Bezique", undated (Box 3)
  - "The Cousins" by Marty Kingsbury, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Keri Hulme, 1985-1990 (Box 3)
  - "A Diary of Passion" by Sandra Shotlander, 2006 (Box 3)
  - "Full Circle" by Sandra Shotlander, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Feminist Theatres survey, December, 1978 (Box 3)
  - "Sister of Fire" by Marty Kingsbury, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Rosemary Keefe: Feminist Theatre Archives (1), 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Rosemary Keefe: Feminist Theatre Archives (2), 1983-1995 (Box 3)
  - Lesbian Playwrights - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 3)
  - Amagon All Stars (AAS) - correspondence with playwrights, 1992-1995 (Box 3)
  - "Belles Lettres Interviews" with Australian Feminist playwrights, 1986 (Box 3)
  - MLA Forum: Theatre of Black and Third World Women - "Drama of the Solitary Black Woman", 1981 (Box 3)
  - Articles on Feminist and Black Theatres, 1979-1987 (Box 3)
  - "Enid's Fly Trap" by Terry Baum, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Martha Boesing, 1971-1990 (Box 3)
  - The National Festival of Women's Theatre, 1983-1985 (Box 3)
  - Melkweg Festival - Amsterdam, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Summer New York City Theatre, 1983 (Box 3)